{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","address":"16956-58 E Warren Ave","zipcode":"48224","owner":"Krystal Enterprises LLC","licenseNumber":"208185","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"4/27/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E610000070418DAD8DCD54C030CA56ABF72B4540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"44033","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","inspectionDate":"2018-11-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"3","ccount":"3","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"3","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"44033","inspectionDate":"11/5/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"LOBBY/ (Customer Waiting Area)","subLocation":"No Thermometer(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"44033","inspectionDate":"11/5/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"No Test strips","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"A designated dressing room/area shall be provided and used."},{"inspectionid":"44033","inspectionDate":"11/5/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All of the following food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American national standards institute, utilizing the conference for food protection standards:  (a) A food service establishment that is not any of the following:    (i) Operating under a temporary food service establishment license.  (ii) A vending machine location.     (b) An extended retail food establishment.  (c) Operated within a retail grocery.  (2) An individual certified under subsection (1) shall be recognized with full faith and credit by the state and all local units of government throughout the state.  (3) The department may promulgate rules to do all of the following:  (a) Develop requirements for retail food establishments to follow when employing certified food safety managers or personnel.  (b) Set a reasonable date for compliance with the requirements under subdivision (a) taking into consideration existing local personnel certification requirements.  (c) Establish certification fees necessary to implement, maintain, and track certified individuals directly or by contract. The department may annually adjust the schedule of fees to provide that the fee charged is sufficient to cover the cost of the certification tracking program.  (d) Implement and enforce the requirements described in subdivision (a).    (4) The certification program developed by the American national standards institute, as it exists on April 1, 2008 , is incorporated by reference. The department may adopt updates to the certification program accreditation standards in subsection (1) by rule.     (5) This section does not prohibit any local legislative body from implementing a food handler program, an employee health certification program, or a manager certification program, if it is not in conflict with this section.","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the PERSON IN CHARGE","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide manufacture lable "},{"inspectionid":"44033","inspectionDate":"11/5/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"4-601.11","violationDescription":"(A) EQUIPMENT FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES and UTENSILS shall be clean to sight and touch. (Pf)\r\n(B) The FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of cooking EQUIPMENT and pans shall be kept free of encrusted grease deposits and other soil accumulations. \r\n(C) NonFOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be kept free of an accumulation of dust, dirt, FOOD residue, and other debris. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"Equipment slicer","problemDescription":"Soiled","subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the Slicer","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."},{"inspectionid":"44033","inspectionDate":"11/5/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing Hand washing signage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-05T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"44033","inspectionDate":"11/5/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing Thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-08T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make available at all times."}]},{"inspectionid":"40583","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","inspectionDate":"2017-10-26T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"2","ccount":"0","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"0","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40583","inspectionDate":"10/26/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"40583","inspectionDate":"10/26/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing Thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2017-11-07T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"}]},{"inspectionid":"36847","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","inspectionDate":"2016-10-18T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"1","pfcount":"2","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"3","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"3","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36847","inspectionDate":"10/18/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"probe","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"No Food thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Make available at all times."},{"inspectionid":"36847","inspectionDate":"10/18/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"No Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"36847","inspectionDate":"10/18/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"ceiling(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"Missing Ceiling tile(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36847","inspectionDate":"10/18/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"6-501.114","violationDescription":"The PREMISES shall be free of items that are unnecessary to the operation or maintenance of the establishment such as EQUIPMENT that is nonfunctional, no longer used and free of litter.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Unnecessary item(s)","subItem":"old/broken equipment","problemDescription":"Not removed from facility","subProblem":"","location":"REAR PREP AREA","subLocation":"At the UNNECESSARY ITEMS","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove from facility/premises."},{"inspectionid":"36847","inspectionDate":"10/18/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"2-102.20","violationDescription":"A PERSON IN CHARGE who demonstrates knowledge by being a FOOD protection manager that is certified by a FOOD protection manager certification program that is evaluated and listed by a Conference for Food Protection-recognized accrediting agency as conforming to the Conference for Food Protection Standards for Accreditation of Food Protection Manager Certification Programs is deemed to comply with Â¶ 2-102.11(B).","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Food Protection Manager","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"No Certified Manager","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"36847","inspectionDate":"10/18/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"REAR STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"At the Wall (back)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"36847","inspectionDate":"10/18/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1459","name":"Rob's Deli","violationCode":"3-304.15","violationDescription":"(A) SINGLE-USE gloves shall be used for one task only and discarded when      damaged, soiled, or when interruptions occur in the operation. (P)\r\n\r\n(B) Slash-resistant and cloth gloves shall be used in direct contact only with FOOD that is subsequently cooked. Gloves used with ready-to-eat foods shall be smooth,   durable and non-absorbant.\r\n","violationType":"Priority","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Single-use glove(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"No SINGLE USE GLOVES","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-10-31T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1459"}}